

JATIN CHANCHALANI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

2 8107767303

✓ jatin200020@gmail.com

3 THA 5 Jawahar Nagar,302004 Jaipur (India)

https://jatinchanchalaniportf
olio.netlify.app/

KEY TECKNOLOGIES

- ReactJs
- AngularJs
- NodeJs
- PHP (Laravel)
- SQL and NoSQL
- Git
- Mongodb

EDUCATION

SECONDARY

SENIOR SECONDARY
 Maheshwari Public School

2017-2018 Per - **75.8**%

 BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY
 Anand International College of Engineering

PROFILE

I have one year and six months of development, designing, and database management expertise. I am a trained and experienced web and app developer.

I'm imaginative, have strong analytical and problem-solving abilities, and I'm a detail-oriented team player.

EXPERIENCE

1.) SYNORIQ

January 2022 - Present

Projects I worked for that company include:

- Loan Originating System with handling Web Portal, CRM and teamapp with creating lead flow.
- UPSTOX (Profile)
- Supply Chain Product with SAAS development
- Collection App for Finova nbfc Bank and handling with client side

Description

- Make a API on NodeJS and PHP(Laravel)
- Angular(Ionic) used for app development.
- ReactJs used in upstox project
- PHP routing and worked on CRM
- Database Management and Done Support Task on daily baises with resolving bugs and make new features.
- Develop SAAS product of Supply Chain in Synoriq using ReactJS Development

2.) IBM Skillsbuild (Internship)

December 2021 - January 2022

- Make a Food website on HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Also used bootstrap for responsive website